{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The primary function of the bias circuit is to", "opta": "hold the circuit stable at VCC", "optb": "hold the circuit stable at vin", "optc": "ensure proper gain is achieved", "optd": "hold the circuit stable at the designed Q-point", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A JFET", "opta": "is a current-controlled device", "optb": "has a low input resistance", "optc": "is a voltage-controlled device", "optd": "is always forward-biased", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A source follower has a voltage gain (Av) of", "opta": "AV = gmRd", "optb": "AV = gmRS", "ans": "", "explanation": ""}, {"question": "The capacitor that produces an ac ground is called a(n)", "opta": "coupling capacitor", "optb": "dc open", "optc": "bypass capacitor", "optd": "ac open", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The formula used to calculate the approximate ac resistance of the base-emitter diode (re) is", "opta": "", "optb": "re  25 mV \u00d7 IC", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The signal voltage gain of an amplifier, Av, is defined as:", "opta": "", "optb": "Av = IC \u00d7 RC", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a class B push-pull amplifier, the transistors are biased slightly above cutoff to avoid", "opta": "crossover distortion", "optb": "unusually high efficiency", "optc": "negative feedback", "optd": "a low input impedance", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The depletion-mode MOSFET", "opta": "can operate with only positive gate voltages", "optb": "can operate with only negative gate voltages", "optc": "cannot operate in the ohmic region", "optd": "can operate with positive as well as negative gate voltages", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Three different points are shown on a dc load line. The upper point represents the", "opta": "minimum current gain", "optb": "quiescent point", "optc": "saturation point", "optd": "cutoff point", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following conditions are needed to properly bias an npn transistor amplifier?", "opta": "Forward bias the base/emitter junction and reverse bias the base/collector junction.", "optb": "Forward bias the collector/base junction and reverse bias the emitter/base junction.", "optc": "Apply a positive voltage on the n-type material and a negative voltage on the p-type material.", "optd": "Apply a large voltage on the base.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Often a common-collector will be the last stage before the load; the main function of this stage is to", "opta": "provide voltage gain", "optb": "buffer the voltage amplifiers from the low-resistance load", "optc": "provide phase inversion", "optd": "provide a high-frequency path to improve the frequency response", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In order for feedback oscillators to have any practical value, the gain has to be", "opta": "< 1", "optb": "self-adjusting", "optc": "stabilized", "optd": "nonlinear", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To get a negative gate-source voltage in a self-biased JFET circuit, you must use a", "opta": "voltage divider", "optb": "source resistor", "optc": "ground", "optd": "negative gate supply voltage", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}